(Leonard:)On the other hand, some physicists are
concerned that if this supercollider works...
...it'll create a black hole and swallow up
the Earth, ending life as we know it.
(Raj:)What a bunch of crybabies.
(Raj:)No guts, no glory, man.
(Leonard(looking at an orange notice on the noticeboard):)Hey, check it out.
(Leonard(looking at an orange notice on the noticeboard):)The School of Pharmacology
is looking for volunteers.
"We are testing a new medication
for social anxiety...
(Raj:)...panic attacks, agoraphobia
and obsessive-compulsive disorder."
(Raj:)Why would they be looking
for test subjects here?
(Leonard:)I don't know, Raj.
Maybe the comic-book store
doesn't have a bulletin board.
- What's going on?
- Shh! Hot girl in Sheldon's office.
(Leonard:)Sheldon's office?
(Leonard:)Is she lost?
(Missy:)I don't think so.
I followed her here from the parking lot.
- Maybe she's his lawyer.
- Well, she's free to examine my briefs.
(Sheldon:)- Howard...
- I know, I'm disgusting.
(Howard:)I should be punished.